You know without you I’m so lonely
When you’re not here 911 calling
Into your heat again I’m diving
Darling you Darling you baby
Fighting round in circles where is the way out
‘Cause I know that our love was hotter than the sun
Yeah the taste of this tequila I’m drinking now
Isn’t bitter than my heart
(If you know this)
I want to know our problem blood type or DNA
Friends see my feed and worry, do you babe? Yeah
Been waiting for your call every night
But I can’t wait no more
Dialing you-u-u, sorry darling you
You know without you I’m so lonely
When you’re not here 911 calling
Into your heat again I’m diving
Darling you Darling you baby
You know without you I’m so lonely
If you won’t be here 911 calling
Falling to you I’m always diving
Darling you Darling you baby
Darling with me under the sun
I know that you’re my one
I don’t wanna let you go
I can’t think of being alone
What am I supposed to do
And I gotta let you know
You got my heart like it’s yours
Don’t wanna say goodbye
(If you know this)
I want to know our problem blood type or DNA
Friends see my feed and worry, do you babe? Yeah
Been waiting for your call every night
But I can’t wait no more
Dialing you-u-u, sorry darling you
You know without you I’m so lonely
When you’re not here 911 calling
Into your heat again I’m diving
Darling you Darling you baby
You know without you I’m so lonely
If you won’t be here 911 calling
Falling to you I’m always diving
Darling you Darling you
I see you, you see me
I care for you, you care for me
We can be all we need
Promise I won’t take you for granted never
I’ma treat you better (I’ma treat you better)
I’ma see you better (I’ma see you better)
So honey now come into my arms yeah
Kiss me baby
You know without you I’m so lonely
When you’re not here 911 calling
Into your heat again I’m diving
You know without you I’m so lonely
If you won’t be here 911 calling
Falling to you I’m always diving
Darling you Darling you baby